<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<changelog xmlns="http://ddaysoftware.com/ChangeLog">
    <version number="0.19">
        <features>
            <improved>
                <summary>
                    Automatically set/unset the "Completed" time of Todo items when the status changes.
                </summary>
            </improved>
            <improved>
                <summary>
                    Moved all common properties of Event, Todo, and Journal components to the UniqueComponent class.
                </summary>                
            </improved>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added a Copy() method to all iCalObject-based objects (pretty much everything).                    
                </summary>
                <details>
                    You can now do things like this:
                    <p>
                        iCalendar iCal1 = iCalendar.LoadFromFile(@"MyFile.ics");
                        iCalendar iCal2 = iCal1.Copy(); // Make a copy of the entire calendar
                        
                        Event evt = iCal1.Events[0].Copy(); // Make a copy of the first event
                        Todo todo = iCal1.Todos[0].Copy(); // Make a copy of the first todo
                        Journal journal = iCal1.Journals[0].Copy(); // Make a copy of the first journal entry
                    </p>
                    <p>This is new functionality.  Please let me know if you find any bugs with it: doug AT dday[NOSPAM]software.com</p>
                </details>
            </added>
        </features>        
    </version>
    <version number="0.18" released="2006-10-10">
        <summary>
            <p>
                Version 0.18 is here! This version fixes a lot of bugs from version 0.17, and made
                many improvements to the serialization framework.  It also contains improvements
                to all iCalendar objects by providing additional useful methods.
            </p>
            <p>
                Another useful feature introduced in version 0.18 is the ability to setup
                custom iCalendar objects to be loaded in place of the standard iCalendar,
                Event, Todo, Journal, Alarm, TimeZone, etc.  This is very useful to be able
                to add custom functionality to the built-in classes without added a lot of
                overhead.
            </p>
        </summary>
        <features>
            <improved>
                <summary>Improved implicit casting to and from iCal data types.</summary>
            </improved>
            <improved>
                <summary>Moved the 'Sequence' field from Event, Todo, and Journal to the RecurringComponent object.</summary>
            </improved>
            <improved>
                <summary>
                    Items must now be explicitly serialized by attaching the SerializedAttribute attribute
                    to each public field or property to be serialized.
                </summary>
            </improved>
            <added>
                <summary>Added the RemoveChild() method to all iCalObject-based items.</summary>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added support for custom iCalendar objects and custom iCalendar component objects
                    (Event, Todo, Journal, Alarm, etc.).
                </summary>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added english-language parsing of recurrence patterns.                    
                </summary>
                <details>
                    Things like "Every other month, on day 21", "Every day at 6:00PM",
                    and "Every 3rd month on the last tuesday and wednesday" should
                    resolve to a proper recurrence pattern.
                    <note>
                        Recurrence patterns must begin with "Every", and each additional
                        constraint should be separated with a comma.  For example:
                        "Every month on the first sunday, at 5:00PM, and at 7:00PM"
                    </note>
                </details>
            </added>
        </features>
    </version>
    <version number="0.17" released="2006-08-31">
        <summary>
            <p>
                Version 0.17 has arrived! I've just completed the serialization
                framework for DDay.iCal!  For those confused by the previous statement,
                let me rephrase: You can now save an iCalendar into an .ics format.
            </p>
            <p>
                There are now over 80 tests that are performed on the libraries
                to ensure proper behavior.  Among these are new tests to ensure
                serialization works properly.  To run these tests, simply run
                DDay.iCal.Test.exe.  To view the results of the serialization tests,
                look in "Calendars\Serialization\Temp".
            </p>
        </summary>
        <features>            
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added iCalendar serialization (saving).                    
                </summary>
                <details>
                    I've added support for saving back to a .ics (RFC 2445) format.
                    I've also added a new series of tests to ensure the correct 
                    functionality of serialization in DDay.iCal.Test.Exe.  The tests
                    load a series of calendars and then save them in the Calendars\Serialization\Temp
                    folder with "_Serialized" added to the file name.  Let me know
                    if you find any bugs with the serialization behavior!
                </details>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Unique components (components with a UID, namely Event, Todo, and Journal objects)
                    can now be accessed from the iCalendar object by UID.
                </summary>
                <details>
                    For example,
<code>
iCalendar iCal = iCalendar.LoadFromFile("calendar.ics");
if (iCal != null)
{
    Event evt = iCal.Events["420a59c8-c4f0-48ff-8539"];
    if (evt != null)
        MessageBox.Show(evt.Summary);
}
</code>
                </details>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added the ability to merge multiple calendars together into a single calendar.
                </summary>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added support for BASE64, 8BIT, and 7BIT encoding on various data types.
                </summary>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added support for binary and uri-based attachments for components.
                </summary>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added support for SENT-BY, CN, and DIR properties of a calendar address (Cal_Address).
                </summary>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added support for the FMTYPE (MIME type) property of attachments.
                </summary>
            </added>
        </features>        
    </version>
    <version number="0.16" released="2006-08-14">
        <summary>
            <p>
                I've completed the next release of the DDay.iCal library, version 0.16.
                Currently all major components are working, and I'm beginning to test them
                on the Enterprise application level, with very good success.
            </p>
            <p>
                For each release, the DDay.iCal project is tested with extensive routines
                built using the NUnit libraries.  Currently, over 60 tests are performed
                to ensure that every element of the library behaves as expected.
            </p>
        </summary>
        <features>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added support for ALARM components. You can now poll events and todo items for alarm times.
                </summary>
            </added>
            <added>
                <summary>
                    Added support for JOURNAL components. You can now work with journal entries.
                </summary>
            </added>
            <improved>
                <summary>
                    Greatly improved the display of iCalendar objects in debuggers.
                </summary>
            </improved>
            <improved>
                <summary>
                    Improved documentation on all classes; most classes should have a class summary,
                    and the most-used classes should have examples.
                </summary>
            </improved>
        </features>         
        <notes>
            <note ts="2006-08-14 4:50PM">I've applied a BSD-variation license to the DDay.iCal project.</note>
        </notes>
    </version>
    <version number="0.15" released="2006-08-08">
        <summary>Initial release - todo and events should be working.</summary>
    </version>
</changelog>